Before the lecture, we will interact with you.
There is a small window under our dynamic.
The purpose of this vote is mainly to understand the use of everyone.
Provide everyone with a better and better mouth software.
So in the dynamic, we put a small vote.
There is only one question in it.
The first to come in can vote first.
If you use a computer, you can pull it down directly.
You can see the dynamic we send.
If you look at the phone,
You can shrink the whole screen first.
Then click on the anchor.
Then the dynamic can be filled in a questionnaire.
Fill in is a clear vote.
So you can choose your own real situation.
Then we will respond to everyone's situation.
Then we will give the future to a more optimized software for Chinese users.
OK.
Then we are going to talk about the next module.
A module-based course.
First of all, why do we have this function?
And what is this function used for?
Cloud is an all-rounder.
Each position.
We all need to use the position.
So in the designer's use,
Mainly need to arrange analysis.
The designer is not particularly strong about analysis.
So in order to improve this function,
Divide the clothing version into different parts.
Then the designer can directly switch each part.
Then combine into a piece of clothing.
Make a set of clothes for the design.
And then a set of clothes can be redesigned.
For example, I want to add a section.
Then make a cross section.
Or add a pocket and so on.
Then we first see a shirt.
I already installed it.
You can go to the next screen.
Well, you can see that the module drawing has a module drawing change option here, and there is also a module drawing in this mode.
So what's the difference between the two? First of all, the first module drawing change option is mainly designed to be used more often. It can be a
change of a module and then import it into the warehouse for a free assembly of clothing.
What about the module drawing? It's a module creation. First of all, we click on this module drawing mode
And then you can see that one of its interfaces is a module editor
And then if you look down here on the right, there's a module drawing model preset value
Let's click on the left mouse button
You can see that there's a row of modules on top of it and then there's a row of modules that correspond to each module
For example, this is a shirt and then we choose a shirt and then there's a folding one
The model and then there's a basic model and then there's a short sleeve and then we choose a basic model here and then we click OK
Oh, hold it for a little bit when I got it
And then you can see that it's just one of its interfaces on top of every module frame and then under that's part of its module structure
So let's first look at the linear disrupted line tool and we can see that each module is gradually
Has a
As long as we put the board into the module frame and then the board and the module frame are tested,
their system will identify which test line is to be tested.
First of all, we need to put the board into the module frame.
You can see each module frame above.
Let's click on it.
You can see that the corresponding module frame below will present a black border.
For example, you can see a collar above.
So we find the plate of the collar and select all the frames.
Then put it into the module frame.
Then select the front piece.
Then you can see that the frame selection is all front pieces.
Then put it into the module frame.
The module frame will be designed according to its size.
It automatically enlarges and shrinks.
Then the back piece.
Select the back piece.
Then put it into the module frame of the back piece.
Then the sleeve.
Pay attention to the sleeve.
Don't put it back.
Don't put it back left and right.
We can just put it down here.
Then the sleeve on the right side.
Put it down.
Then there are two seam allowances.
After putting it in, you can see that some parts are overlapping.
Right?
We can adjust it.
Just move the module frame directly.
Then after putting it in.
We will do a foundation.
Let's take a look at it first.
In the case of each module foundation,
there are corresponding module frames.
They are all randomly connected.
So if we do a foundation,
we only need to do a foundation with the panel and the module frame.
There is no need to do a foundation with the panel and the panel.
Let's take a look at it first.
We use the free foundation tool.
To be able to do a foundation with the panel and the module frame.
Then look at this point.
This point is a knife.
It is aligned to the shoulder line.
So I must make a foundation for the knife.
Don't use the edge.
The edge will simulate an bulge.
So it's going down from the knife.
It will show a dark black when the foundation is finished.
And then there is a foundation line.
It automatically.
A random creation.
It becomes one of its own colors
So if you sew it like this
If it corresponds to sewing
He will the system will ink this section
It's sewn together with this section
So we sewed this section, too
Sew from the thread down
So as long as these two sections are sewn
The system will know if it's inked
Okay, this section is with this section
It's sewn together
And then we sew the other side
Oh, here and the module frame
That's the point
Uh, the knife of the sewing line
The direction must not be reversed
If it's reversed
Uh, you can delete it and then sew it again
Or choose his right arrow and then change the sewing line
Oh, be careful of the knife to sew down
Oh, the other side
The next time
Then the back sleeve
Sew it well
Use the shift button
To refine with 1 to n
And then release the shift button
Can finish refining
And the other side
Use the shift button
To refine
There is also another side of the sleeve, use the knife to sew down.
If you want to sew, you can use the thread to sew.
Just press two points and you can sew.
If you want to sew, don't turn the sewing line in the opposite direction.
I sewed the side seam.
There is also a 1 to n seam in the front.
There are two sections here, press the SHIFT key to sew these two sections.
Then the other side, press the SHIFT key to sew two sections.
And then the shoulder line.
Press the SHIFT key to sew these two sections.
And then the side seam in the back.
Sew both sides.
And then the shoulder line.
Press the SHIFT key to sew these two sections.
If you want to sew, don't turn the knife.
If you want to move your hand, press the upper edge button to turn the sewing line to the back.
Decorate your bag to see if this bag is soft or not.
This bag and worried me.
I have separate vidéos about this bag.
Check them out.
I don't write what I said I didn't keep a secret.
Because this bag is my business.
All you have to do is shower.
Just sew it up like this
And this piece and this piece of thread
And this piece of thread is sewn down directly
Just don't turn the line of thread
down
And the next part of the sleeve is a little bit easier
Just sew the two ends up and down and sew the two ends of the thread
You can take a look at this part of the sleeve
It's going to be a little bit difficult
I'll sew it up and you'll have a look
Sew the long side first
And then press the long side
Press the shift key
First sew the sleeve
This little plate is sewn up
This is the overlapping part
We start from this point
Sew it this way
Then skip the fold part
From this point
Sew to the end
Then turn it around
Then sew to the point of opening the sleeve
Then press the left key
Then release the shift key
Then you can complete a piece of sleeve
This is the seam of the sleeve
Let's take a look at the result
After sewing
It's like this
If you can't see it clearly
I'll sew it again
It's a long piece of sewing
Then press the shift key
Sew this little piece of sleeve
Then press this point
Then sew it over
Skip the fold part
Then start from this point
Then sew it this way
Then turn it around
Start from this point
End at the point of opening
Press the left key
Then release the shift key
Then you can complete a piece of seam
If the seam is good
You can check
Did the seam open
Or no seam
Then you can look at this side
I didn't sew with the mold
Because it doesn't need to cross the panel
Seam with another panel
So as long as the panel
Seam with the panel
For example, the bottom plate
No need to be sewed with the mold
For example, no sleeve
A sleeve
This side of the sleeve
No need to be sewed with the mold
Then I look up and see that there is a tool here, the module sewing line display and the panel sewing line display, you can switch the display, you can see which one you need to choose, look at your personal hobbies, you can choose one.
After sewing, we are going to keep a module, and before we keep the module, we will simulate it first. You can see that there are some holes in this, right?
You can see that there is a gray state here, which means it is locked. At this time, we just need to find this front piece.
Front piece
Then
Press it again, and then press it again, and then you can activate a lock for all of them.
Then we simulate it again.
Pause the simulation.
I can take a look.
Then the system will make a seam by default.
Then the next step is to make a 3D quick shot.
Why do we need to make a quick shot?
Because when we keep the module, we need to add a
And then build a new file.
The name of this file is named a name.
And then we talk about this window.
Then the size of the preview here, choose the smallest one, because it's just a preview.
Then you can hide the model here, or you can hide it.
If you hide it, the effect will be a little better.
Then here is the model.
Then here is the transparent background.
You can choose a transparent background.
Then click save.
Then our next step is.
How to save this module.
Then see there is a module editor below.
The mouse is placed in each module frame.
It has two small icons in the upper right corner.
One to open and one to save.
Then the second one, this is the save module.
Let's click the left button to click.
Then find the folder.
Then build a new file.
Then name it as Zheng Shan.
Then open it.
Then just default the name.
Then click save.
Then a window will pop up.
Save file.
An extractor.
An extractor of a module file.
And a new extractor.
Then the first extractor of a module file.
Is a system default.
An extractor of a vertical perspective.
Then a new extractor below.
For example, I want to measure this vertical.
Then.
A vertical perspective.
At this time, you can measure it in advance.
Then take a quick photo.
Then add it here.
Just add a picture of your quick photo.
Then here I directly choose to use the module file.
It's just a default extractor of the system.
Then click confirm.
Then it will pop up another window.
It is an extractor of this module frame.
You can see it here.
The file name is a format of ZMD2.
Then the extractor below.
Let's click this plus.
Let's click the left button.
Click.
Then it will.
Then find us.
Just.
A picture saved.
This is what I saved before.
Let me click.
Then click open.
Then you can see a extractor of it.
Then click confirm.
Then you can see that the other words are locked.
Only the white part is not locked.
You can see that the white words are just a default extractor.
This part.
Then according to.
The method of storing the collar.
We put the following few modules.
One by one.
Then select.
At the top of the selection bar.
Then a save button.
Let's click on it.
Then save it to the default file folder before.
Then click save directly.
Then select the default one directly.
An extractor of a module file.
Then click confirm.
The selected one is.
It is in a state of activation.
Then click save.
Just click save.
Then save.
Save in a file folder.
Wait a minute.
When it's convenient for us to go into this module.
It will.
All.
In a file folder.
Then click confirm directly.
Then there is.
Fixed.
Then save.
Then click confirm.
Then some other modules have been saved.
Then.
For the saved modules.
For example, I want to make some changes to a module.
For example, I want to keep this collar.
Keep one or two or three more modules.
At this point.
We can do a module.
A combination.
Or a module.
Keep a new module.
We are at the window of the library.
Then put in a file of the collar.
Then just click no.
Then select the type to be added.
Then click confirm.
OK.
That collar.
That collar has come in, right?
Before I tell how to save other collars, let's talk about that.
I talked about it before the live broadcast.
We will have a small interaction with everyone.
There is a small window of voting in our
dynamic seconds.
That voting is to understand the use of others.
Then it provides us with a better approach.
to optimize a better dog software
so set up such a vote
that did not hear before, then
the little friends can now go to a vote
so if you use the computer to see the live broadcast, then
you can directly pull down
to see our one dynamic page
and then directly click on the vote can
vote that there is only one question in it
so relatively simple
you can now go to a vote
on the phone, then you can switch it to the smallest picture
and then click on the live broadcast
and then click on the dynamic
to make a vote
that vote is a secret vote
so you can rest assured
to vote according to your own real situation
now you can
go to a vote
let's wait a little bit
that we start to talk about
how to keep some other modules
such as this collar
I want to keep another one
to keep a few more modules
such as we choose first
to use this collar
and then I put it
away to your model
and then you can see at this time
he this collar after leaving
or to see this
there is a Siu-Lin relationship right
that you are at this time
to move this board to the outside of the frame
his Siu-Lin line is also automatically deleted
by delete
the
Wait a moment
You can take a look
Then we select it
Then activate it first
Then, for example, put this collar
Put it around the neck of the virtual model
Convenient to simulate
Let's adjust it a little bit
Then we put this plate into a model frame of the collar
Then there is no sewing line at this time
So we have to re-sew it
Then we use the sewing line first
Can be sewed with a thread
Then you can see that there are knives here
Just sew the knife to the knife
Just sew it down
Sewing, then, is also
Just don't sew the sewing line in the opposite direction
Just sew it down
After sewing, you can see here
It has a sewing line display
You can see here that it has been sewn, right?
At least we need to simulate
First of all, I put these other one
The plate is re-activated
Re-activated
Then this one of the plates
We can directly select it on the side of the collar
You can see it only activates
Only activate the module
Let's click on it
The other one presents a gray state
It means it's locked
Only this collar is not locked
At least we can simulate
You can also see that only the collar is simulated
And pause the simulation
For this simulated collar
The module
We can save it
You are looking for a module frame of the collar
Then here is the second save button
Click
Then directly save to
One of the default files before
Then click save
Then click confirm directly
Then the second collar module is saved
Then we will show another one
For example, I put this collar
Also a preservation
First of all, we select it
Move it away
Then re-activate
Then move it out of the module frame
Outside
Move it out of the module frame
Move it back
Move it down
Move it in the switch
And then re-activate
Re-activate
Then we activate the other module frame
A new module, once again
Look at the model
We can see it
Like this, and then activate it, and then put it into the module frame.
The module frame will automatically zoom in or out according to the size of the board.
And then the powder, the powder, is also a powder for the blade.
The direction of the powder line should not be reversed.
After the powder is finished, you can start the simulation.
After the simulation is done, we will save it again.
Select the module frame, and then the second save button on it.
Click the left button.
And then it is also saved in a file folder before.
Then click Save.
Then click Confirm.
Then the three
A window of our module
First of all, I switch to the simulation mode here
Then zoom in
You can see that there is still a module frame here, right?
At this time, you can directly
Right click on the blank place in the 2D window
Find the delete module relationship
Click and then click yes
Its one module frame can be deleted by us
Then we first select the edit version
Adjust the version tool to select the version
Delete all versions first
Later we will demonstrate how to use this
A window with module conversion options
I'll shrink this first
Then take a look at the module conversion options
There is a default system below
There are three files
A foldable one
A module frame of a male and a female
First, let's click on this
A module frame of the foldable shirt
Let's hide the model first
Then just double click one
Just double click a module frame
Then you can see these
Its one
Each part
For example, let's type a collar
And the front
As long as you double click
You can quickly make a switch
And the back
There is also a sleeve
This is
And then the back
You can just double click into it
Then you can see
A module of the foldable shirt here
The shirt here is only half
But for example
If you sometimes do these
For convenience
You can add this shirt
Just cut it off
And then just keep what you need
Just a part
Then we first click this
Then double click to go back to the top
Then we don't need these
You just select
Just delete it
Then see the module drawing change option
Then below
Then look to the right
There is an increase button
Let's click
Then we find
A file holder that was previously stored
Then select it
Select the file holder
Pour it in
Then select this
Use this basic one
Double-click
You can see
This is what I did before
A preserved one
That's what I did before
Some modules
below
Then on the right side of the increase
There is a reset button
For example
A file you added
You don't need it
You can click this reset
It will
Restore to default
A file of the system
A module that was previously imported
Will be deleted
There is also a update below
For example, this module
You added another before
For example, a customer service
There is no display here
You can click this update button
It will refresh
Then look below
There is an edit
Let's click
Then it can perform a module display
This is hidden
You can take a look here
Then here
There is an add group
What is the use of this function
For example
You have one of these modules
It has two clothes of different sizes
Then if you directly save it
This file
In the file folder
Then switch
Then you may put
A large size collar
Then pin to
A small size
On the front
So the simulation is definitely not possible
So you can add a group here
Make a classification of them
Then on the right
There is an add module structure
And keep this module structure file
Then look up
There is a finished edit
Click the end button
Then we just click this
For an end
Then we click no
Then click no
Then for this module
For example
I can directly double click
Put this collar module
Enter
Show this model
And then double click this collar
That designer can
Now you can
Do it quickly
To do a quick
A change of structure
A change of parts
And then
To combine
A different one
Clothes
Back
Let's double click it
Put it in
Then
Embroider
And then
Embroidery
There is a embroidery
Clothes
And then
Embroidery
And there is
Clothes
And then
Embroidery
Clothes
After that, you can take a look at a piece of clothing and it will be quickly combined and then we can simulate it.
Okay, and then for this, the designer can make different changes. For example, this collar, I want to change one, just double-click to switch
And then, for example, the front, I'll change one, too.
And then the sleeves, let's switch one
And then there's the cuff.
Let's switch one every time.
That way, another piece of clothing will be quickly switched, right?
Take a look and then simulate
So for the clothes that have been switched, the designer can do a design here
For example, you don't need this model frame. You can see it in the open space at the door of the second floor and delete it from the model frame.
I'll click yes
And then we're going to shrink this first
And then, for example, I just want one side of this pocket and then I don't want this side and I'm going to delete it
I'm going to turn off the bloodline directly
And then, for example, I want to make a separation line and I want to separate two pieces in the front and I'm going to choose a 3D drawing
And then we're going to do a split
And then you're going to single out a 3D drawing on the top.
Let me see
No, just wait a minute.
So I saw that I said I didn't have the material for that material.
In the cloud public account, you can get it by replying to the link on the account tài
But if you don't have the material, you can download it by replying to the link on the account.
And then you draw.
And then we finish drawing the line.
Then you can read it.
Let's convert it into an internal shape.
You can see that the shape of this line is not good.
You can make a change.
For example, I click on it first.
You can delete it.
It becomes a straight line.
If you think this is OK, you can select the inner line.
Then right-click to make a cut.
You can see that it is separated.
There are two pieces.
If there are other designs, you can make a change here.
For example, I want to change the fabric.
You can do it.
For example, select these sheets first.
Don't want these two front pieces.
There are back pieces.
Apply a new fabric here.
I can directly paint the window.
Here is the fabric.
Just pick one and drag it over.
That's it.
For some other fabrics.
For example, this piece.
You choose all of them.
You can apply a new fabric.
This can also be applied to a fabric.
Use this.
Then you can make a quick cloth change.
Turn off the internal line display.
And then simulate again.
Okay.
In this way, a piece of clothing has been modified.
You can take a look at a quick modification design.
For this well-designed clothing, you can save it and show it to customers.
Then the live broadcast content is over here.
If you have any questions, you can leave a message in the back.
Directly send chats
Let me emphasize again
I said a vote before I started.
The vote is mainly for
For the sake of the video
I want to know how you use it.
Then return to us
Then we have a more optimized app for the software.
If you haven't voted yet, you can vote in our dynamic.
There's only one question in the vote.
So it's faster to do it.
If the computer is watching the live broadcast, you can drag it down directly.
Then there's a dynamic below.
Then just click on the vote.
If the phone is watching the live broadcast, you can just click on the full screen.
Then click on the live broadcast and then the dynamic.
You can make a vote.
The votes are all anonymous.
So you can choose a real situation.
If you don't see it, there's a replay.
The audience public number.
He will notify you.
If you haven't done the questionnaire, you can go to our dynamic.
Then we will do a fill in the dynamic.
There's only one content in the content.
So it's easier to vote.
If you vote, it's anonymous.
So you can be assured.
A vote according to your actual situation.
If you don't see the previous content, you can go back to the next live broadcast.
Watch it.
How to make a hard material.
You can just click on the vote button.
Then you can vote.
Pick out a hard material.
You can take the material directly.
Assoc over here.
Detail over here.
The line of the gold tail sand and the strength of the bending area.
The line of the gold tail sand is adjusted to 99.
The material will be harder.
We're going to do a statistics after the format course
You can look forward to it
You can make a belt adjustment code with a sheet of paper
For example, you just draw a
small sheet of paper
and then
Then add an internal line to check
Go to confirm
And then transfer it to
And then in the middle, you can draw a small board
And then add one of their rendering thicknesses
I'll add five
And then here's a little bit of a bulge on the outside
You can turn the curve a little bit lower
Look at this effect
OK
You can make it this way
And then a fixed one in the middle
You can draw another small board
Put it here
And then add one of their rendering thicknesses
And then you can turn the curve a little bit lower
And then a fixed one in the middle
You can draw another small board
Look at this effect
And then you can turn the curve a little bit lower
And then a fixed one in the middle
Just do it this way
And then you can do it like this
Then there is an anti-activation and anti-activation mentioned here.
Model drawing, new model drawing.
Let me show you.
I will import one.
You can see that the mouse is placed on it.
Only activate the module.
Click it.
The rest will be locked.
Now I haven't put it in yet.
There is also a powder.
I will delete these first.
I will import one.
I will put the powder in it.
Click it.
The motion will be just like this.
Only activate the module.
The rest will be locked.
The other one is also locked
You can take a look at that
If you need to unlock it all
You can click again to unlock it all
If you want to set it to millimetres, you can set it here
How to define it?
You can set it to a unit
OK
There are also shortcuts and so on
User interface
Then you can see what you said should be here
All units
Then you can choose millimetres and inches
And you can put it here
If there is none, then we're going to end
The question is in
If you look at the mobile phone, you can narrow it down and then click on the anchor and then click on the dynamic to vote.
If you have a computer, you can see it by pulling it down directly.
If there is no problem, it's over.
That's it for today.
Thank you.